Brandon Heberer

Business Analyst

As a recent MBA graduate, I am very excited to start the next phase in my career by applying my education and experience in the private sector. While I enjoyed working for local government over the last four years because of the real-world business experience I gained, I am now capable of taking on even greater challenges and responsibilities within larger organizations. I have a proven track record of completing progressively complex projects which helped increase productivity, improve interoffice communication, track performance, measure outcomes, and have a positive impact on accountability. I am extremely confident that I will be able to transfer my skillset to your organization while taking very little time to adapt and build relationships.

-EXPERIENCE-

Jun 2015 - Dec 2018

Staff Analyst III

Dept. of Public Health

- Reduced a backlog of more than 2,800 pending Service Authorization Requests to just over 100 at any given time
- Created reports to track employee performance and increase accountability
- Implemented SQL databases that improved interoffice communication, gave managers the ability to track performance, and eliminated data entry duplication between staff members
- Transitioned the division to 90% paperless by implementing business rules and routing logic with the document management system Laserfiche
- Generated RFPs, reviewed responses, and awarded vendors
- Served as liaison to the Fresno County Board of Supervisors
- Secured an \$11.3 million State grant, oversaw implementation of the program, and monitored vendor performance
- Transferred Maintenance and Transportation Request responsibilities from supervisors to line staff by creating workflow diagrams and SOP's thereby turning the normal 45-day turnaround time into an average of three business days
- Implemented and administered the Division's SharePoint site
- · Generated and managed all Division contracts

Apr 2010 - Jun 2015

Assistant Manager

VIOC, Inc.

- Transitioned from CSR to Assistant Manager within one year
- Generated and interpreted P&L reports for upper management
- Increased sales by 40% due to training programs that I developed
- Supervised a diverse staff of 10 employees with varying responsibilities

-EDUCATION-

Jan 2016 - Dec 2018

MBA Degree – Finance Focus

CSU, Fresno

CSU, Fresno

- Graduated cum laude (3.5/4.0 GPA)
- Won second place in an investment simulation challenge with a 63% return
- Excelled in the areas of contemporary leadership, organizational behavior, statistical analysis, information systems, and strategy implementation

Jan 2011 - May 2014

BS Degree – Business Administration

- Led a group of five students to victory in a 45-team competition resulting in the reduction of a local hospice's admittance time from 72 to 12 hours by implementing a mobile intake process while remaining HIPAA complaint
- Excelled in the areas of financial and managerial accounting, business communication, strategic management, and production operation management

Personal Info

Phone

(559) 472-8525

E-Mail

heberer.brandon@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/brandon-heberer-73050a163/

Skills

Problem Solving

Advanced

Oral &Written
Communication

Expert

Leadership

Advanced

Critical Thinking

Expert

Time

Management

Expert

Software

MS Office

Expert

VBA

Advanced

Power BI

Expert

Tableau

•••••
Intermediate

SQL/MySQL

Advanced

Python

•••••
Intermediate

00000

SAP Business

Advanced

PeopleSoft Financials

Objects

Advanced